Privacy Policy
==============

The privacy policy of ExactlyWhatIsTime.com
-------------------------------------------

Effective as of January 1, 2023

As the owner of this website (the “Site”), Taru Technologies Inc (“we” or “us”) understand that your privacy is of critical importance. This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect from you via the Site and how we use and disclose such information.

Our Use of Cookies

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google's privacy policy is available at: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

Advertising

This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a CafeMedia ("CafeMedia") for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and CafeMedia will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about CafeMedia’s data usage, click here: [https://www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy](https://www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy)

Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of this Site, please contact us at info@tarutechnologies.com

Random Pages
------------

* * *

© 2024 ExactlyWhatIsTime.com - Exactly What Is Time?
